{
    "subject": "resource/Duck_Soup_(1933_film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Margaret_Dumont",
    "human_readable": "Duck Soup (1933 film) stars Margaret Dumont.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.792759358882904,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Duck Soup'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847777009010315,
            "question": "Were there any other notable actors in 'Duck Soup' besides Margaret Dumont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7513449192047119,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Margaret Dumont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977663397789001,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Duck Soup' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45211389660835266,
            "question": "What impact did Margaret Dumont's performances have on cinema history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43313220143318176,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Duck Soup' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42521044611930847,
            "question": "Is Margaret Dumont known for any particular type of role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3264514207839966,
            "question": "How might the societal context of the 1930s have influenced the humor in 'Duck Soup'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25728341937065125,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors associated with films from 1933?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06321213394403458,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in comedies from the 1930s?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Duck Soup (1933 film) stars Margaret Dumont.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7705_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous directors associated with films from 1933?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7705_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the societal context of the 1930s have influenced the humor in 'Duck Soup'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7705_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Margaret Dumont known for any particular type of role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7705_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7705_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents explicitly state that Margaret Dumont was a star in \"Duck Soup\" (1933), confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}